GWACHUKWU IKENNA ELEBEKE

PROFILE

Full -stack web developer with experience working with HTML, CSS3/SASS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Vue, NodeJS, ExpressJS, NoSQL (MongoDB) and SQL (Postgres), I build amazing and user-friendly web applications. I am also skilled in Computer Networking (Routing and Switching), Microsoft Azure, Sales and Customer Service. I enjoy working on new products, and occasionally taking on new challenges that push me to grow.

SKILLS

Web Development

HTML, CSS3, SASS, VANILLA JAVASCRIPT, REACT, VUE, TYPESCRIPT, REDUX, VUEX, PHP NODEJS, EXPRESS, SQL (Postgres, MySQL), NoSQL (MongoDB).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer April 2021 - present

Miraton Matador Group, Lekki, Lagos State.

- Build and maintain CloudBank web application
- Develop new user-facing features for MMG subsidiaries' web applications
- Ensure the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs

Software Developer Aug 2020 - April 2021

Cerebre Digital Limited, Opebi, Ikeja, Lagos State.

- Full stack development with HTML5, CSS3/SASS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, PHP
- Use MySQL and PostgreSQL for database development
- · Build software that meet clients' specifications

Software Engineer Nov 2019 - Aug 2020

Stutern Graduate Accelerator, Gbagada, Lagos State.

- Full stack web development.
- Used PostgreSQL/MongoDB for databases development.
- Developed and designed Restful API.
- Collaborating on GitHub, Trello and Slack.

Information and Communications Technology Instructor 2018
KingChuks College Okota, Lagos State

National Youth Service Corps: Educational Instructor 2016-2017 Gaskiya Model School, Katsina, Katsina State.

10B Latunde Close, Ago Palace Way, Okota, Lagos. +2347030821996 / +2348153045001

gwachukwuelebeke@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/gwachukwu **LinkedIn:** https://linkedin.com/in/gwachukwu **Portfolio:** https://gwachukwu.netlify.app

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Mentor Feb 2021 - present

Andela Learning Community and Microsoft I mentor learners in the ALC and Microsoft 4Africa Skillslab

PROJECTS

CloudBank: React, Redux, Bootstrap, SASS. An online banking application that allows users create savings and business accounts, make and monitor their investments and do other financial transactions. https://app.cloudbank.ng

Sound Vault: React, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB.

Audio cloud service application. https://sound-vault.netlify.app

Gwachukwu's bank: React, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB.

A finance tracking app.

https://gwachukwus-bank.netlify.app

CERTIFICATIONS

Cisco Certified Network Associate (Routing and Switching) Aug 2019

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals. Mar 2020

Microsoft Certified: Azure Al Fundamentals Mar 2021

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

BSc. Industrial Chemistry University of Benin, Benin city, Edo State, Nigeria 2015